webce.com 2018-11-13

# WebCE Online Privacy Statement | WebCE

  * Sites Covered by this Privacy Statement
  * Links to Other Sites and Public Forums
  * Collection of Personal Information
  * Cookies
  * Consent
  * Sharing Your Personal Information
  * Data Integrity
  * Security of Your Personal Information
  * Children's Privacy
  * Verification
  * Inquiries, Access and Updating Your Personal Information
  * Contacting Us
  * California Privacy Rights
  * Changes to this Statement

##  Sites Covered by this Privacy Statement

**WebCE, Inc.** ("WebCE") respects your right to privacy. WebCE has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to protect your personal information and your right to privacy. "Personal Information" is any information that can be used to identify an individual, and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical address, title, occupation and other information required to provide our services and products or to carry out a transaction you have requested. 

This statement outlines our Personal Information-handling practices for [www.webce.com](https://www.webce.com/) and related sites (collectively referred to as the WebCE Web site). It does not apply to those sites that do not display or link to this Privacy Statement or that have their own privacy statements. 

This statement is readily available through a link on our home page and at the bottom of every WebCE Web page. Some WebCE programs may have their own, possibly different, privacy policies. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each of the Web sites or program information you visit or review. 

Back to the Top

##  Links to Other Sites and Public Forums 

For your convenience and information, this site may contain links to other sites. If you access those links, you will leave the WebCE website. WebCE does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from WebCE’s practices. WebCE is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of other Web sites by third parties. The Personal Information you choose to provide or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by the WebCE Online Privacy Statement. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your Personal Information. 

WebCE may make message boards, news groups, and/or public forums available to users on its websites. Any information that you disclose in these areas becomes public information that may be accessed by third parties, and you should use caution before deciding to disclose any Personal Information in these forums. 

Back to the Top

##  Collection of Personal Information

WebCE will always tell you before we collect any Personal Information from you and will inform you of the purpose of the collection. "Personal Information" is any information that can be used to identify an individual and may include, but is not limited to, name, email address, postal or other physical address, credit card number, title, occupation and other information required to provide our services and products to you, or to carry out a transact you have requested. WebCE collects Personal Information to operate effectively and to comply with government regulations (e.g., licensing, education, etc.), to comply with contractual obligations. 

The information WebCE collects will be used only as described in this Privacy Statement and/or in the way we specify at the time of collection. We will not subsequently change the way your Personal Information is used without your consent. Some of the ways we may use your Personal Information include, but are not limited to: 

  * Provide the ability to contact you; 
  * To support your Continuing Education; 
  * To administer and process your Continuing Education certification exams; 
  * To report your completion of Continuing Education to comply with government regulations; 
  * To meet contractual obligations with our corporate customers related to Continuing Education of their employees; 
  * To gauge the number of users and usage of the site; 
  * To store information about your preferences; 
  * Recognize you when you return; 
  * To provide information on goods and services requested or which may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes; 
  * Marketing, advertising and promotions, notification of events, surveys, new courses and offerings; and 
  * To notify you about changes to our services; and 
  * To improve the quality of our products and services. 

Personal Information we collect may include the following: 

  * Your username; 
  * Your full name; 
  * Work phone; 
  * Fax number; 
  * Home phone; 
  * Permanent address; 
  * E-mail address; 
  * Order history; 
  * Company name; 
  * Job title, designation and function; 
  * Information regarding professional licenses, license numbers, continuing education and other license-related information, including state of license; 
  * Registration information; 
  * Test results; 
  * Social Security Numbers, where required by law, regulations or contractual obligations. 

WebCE notifies all identified Data Subjects about the purposes for which Personal Information is collected and used. A "Data Subject" is an individual who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by name or other Personal Information. 

In appropriate situations, Personal Information may be "anonymized" so that the identity of individual data subjects cannot be known. In these cases, WebCE will not notify you regarding the purpose for which Personal Information is collected and used by WebCE. 

Back to the Top

##  Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data file transferred by a Web site to your computer's hard drive. WebCE uses cookies to help improve the site and to personalize your visit by customizing our Web pages. WebCE may also collect information about your computer, including your IP address, operating system and browser type. 

Most browsers will accept cookies automatically from the site. You may refuse to accept cookies by adjusting your preferences on your browser. It should be noted that by doing so, you may be unable to access certain pages or areas of the site. 

You can find information on popular browsers and how to adjust your cookie preferences at the following websites: 

  * Microsoft Internet Explorer: <https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies>
  * Google Chrome: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647>
  * Mozilla Firefox: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>
  * Apple Safari: Blocks cookies by default. To change click Safari, Preferences, Security and choose your preference. 

Back to the Top

##  Consent

By using this website and providing Personal Information to us, you fully understand and unambiguously consent to the collection and use of the information as described herein. If we decide to make changes to this Online Privacy Statement, we will post the changes on this site so that you will always know what information we collect, and how we use it. 

Back to the Top

##  Sharing Your Personal Information

We safeguard your privacy interests by ensuring that this WebCE site adheres to our data protection principles described in this statement. 

We may respond to subpoenas, court orders, letters of request from government personnel or legal process by disclosing your Personal Information and other related information, if necessary. We also may disclose your Personal Information when we choose to establish or exercise our legal rights, defend against legal claims or protect our brand and use your Personal Information as appropriate for these purposes. 

WebCE may deal with a number of categories of third parties including service vendors, contractors and authorized third-party agents. We may share Personal Information with service vendors, authorized third-party agents or contractors in order to provide a requested service or transaction, including the processing of orders, processing credit card transaction. We will only provide such third parties with the minimum amount of Personal Information necessary to provide the services on our behalf or to provide services to our customers. These third parties are not permitted to use your Personal Information except for the limited purpose of completing the requested service or transaction. 

We do not sell or rent your Personal Information to third parties for marketing purposes unless you have granted us permission to do so. 

WebCE may also enter into joint marketing or other similar arrangements for the marketing of products or services. For example, WebCE may enter into an agreement for a co-branded website that is jointly owned by WebCE and the joint marketer. In such circumstances, Personal Information collected from the website may be jointly owned by WebCE and the joint marketer. WebCE’s logo will appear on such pages to indicate that the website is "powered by" WebCE. WebCE’s use of the Personal Information collected on such sites will be bound by the terms of this privacy statement. The joint marketer’s use of the Personal Information will be governed by the joint marketer’s privacy statement. 

Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, WebCE decides to sell, buy, merge or otherwise reorganize its business. Such a transaction may involve, in accordance with applicable law, the disclosure of Personal Information to prospective or actual purchasers, or the receipt of it from sellers. It is WebCE’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions. 

We may collect and possibly share Personal Information and any other additional information available to us in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of WebCE's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

WebCE will only share Personal Information about you that is relevant to our legitimate business purposes or as required to meet legal or regulatory requirements. Your Personal Information is never sold or leased to any external company, unless you have granted us permission to do so. 

WebCE does not collect more Personal Information than is needed to fulfill the purposes set forth in this Statement, unless consented to by the data subject or required by contract. 

Should you withdraw consent to the use of your information for any of the above-identified purposes, we will stop using your information for such purposes as soon as it is reasonably possible to do so. WebCE will also notify you if withdrawing consent affects our ability to service you. 

As part of our providing services to our customers, we may share Personal Information from our customers with other third parties as instructed by the customer. We may share the Personal Information with others solely for the purposes of managing the work we are contracted to manage and for no other reason and will abide by any contractual obligations contained in any customer agreement related to the sharing of Personal Information we receive from the customer. 

Back to the Top

##  Data Integrity

WebCE takes reasonable steps to ensure that Personal Information is accurate, complete and current. In the event of changes in your Personal Information, you may inform WebCE to ensure that our information is up-to-date. 

Back to the Top

##  Security of Your Personal Information

WebCE is committed to protecting the Personal Information you share with us. WebCE uses a combination of industry-standard security technologies, procedures, and organizational measures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. WebCE supports online security using secure server technology because we want your data to be safe. There are state-of-the-art security arrangements and facilities on WebCE sites to prevent abuse. 

We bind our employees to observe your privacy and confidentiality rights. 

Back to the Top

##  Children's Privacy

This site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. WebCE does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that data from our systems. 

Back to the Top

##  Verification

WebCE conducts an annual self-assessment in order to verify that this Online Privacy Statement is published and implemented within the Company. 

Back to the Top

##  Inquiries, Access and Updating Your Personal Information

WebCE needs your help in keeping the Personal Information you have shared with us accurate and up-to-date. You may at any time make a written request for access to the Personal Information that WebCE holds about you, in order to review its accuracy and completeness. You have the right to have your Personal Information amended as appropriate. All access requests are subject to relevant access rules and exceptions set out in the laws of the jurisdiction in which the data is located. 

Back to the Top

##  Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement or if you wish to inspect the information we hold about you, please contact:

  **Physical Address:**

WebCE  
12222 Merit Drive  
Suite 500  
Dallas, TX 75251  
ATTN: Privacy Officer  

Back to the Top

##  California Privacy Rights

Residents of the State of California, under California Civil Code § 1798.83, have the right to request from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to which the company has disclosed Personal Information during the preceding year for direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that if the company has a privacy policy that gives either an Opt-out or Opt-in choice for use of your Personal Information by third parties (such as advertisers) for marketing purposes, the company may instead provide you with information on how to exercise your disclosure choice options. 

WebCE qualifies for the alternative option. We have a comprehensive privacy statement, and provide you with details on how you may either Opt-out or Opt-in to the use of your Personal Information by third parties for direct marketing purposes. Therefore, we are not required to maintain or disclose a list of the third parties that received your Personal Information for marketing purposes during the preceding year. 

If you are a California resident and request information about how to exercise your third party disclosure choices, you must send a request to [privacyofficer@webce.com](mailto:privacyofficer@webce.com). 

Back to the Top

##  Changes to this Statement

If we change our privacy statement, we will post the revised statement here, with an updated revision date. If we make significant changes to our statement, we may also notify you by other means, such as sending an email or posting a notice on our home page. 

Back to the Top

Effective Date: June 23, 2011  
© WebCE, Inc., 2011. All rights reserved.
